Pavlos Papadopoulos | Front-End Web Developer







LinkedIn



+306993751715



E mail



Thessaloniki, Greece

Front-End Web Developer, with industry experience building websites and web applications. Translate UX / UI designs to actual code. Also, maintain updated knowledge of new trends and technology. Lately, I'm building projects using Next.js on the front and fetching data from a headless CMS. I'm also familiar with Netlify and AWS platforms.

Experience

Front-End Web Developer

EXEO LP

May 2019 - Present Thessaloniki, Greece

Technologies:

- ➤ ASP.NET Core / DevExtreme UI components
- CSS (Sass) / Bootstrap
- JavaScript (ES6, JQuery, Knockout.js)

Freelance Web Developer

December 2020 - Present

- > Building a website-blog for a medical professional
- > Technologies: Next.js / Strapi headless CMS / Sass

Skills

- > HTML5 / CSS3 (Sass)
- JavaScript (React / Next.js, JQuery, Knockout.js)
- Bundlers (Webpack, Parcel)
- Version Control (Git / TFVC)
- Platforms (Netlify, AWS)

Projects

- Portfolio Page (Next.js Netlify, Ghost headless CMS AWS)
- React App (time machine) My article on dev.to
- React App (video finder)
- Website Layout (globTaste)

Education .

University of Thessaly - <u>MASTER'S DEGREE</u>: AUTOMATION IN AGRICULTURE **Aristotle University** - <u>BACHELOR'S DEGREE</u>: AGRICULTURAL ENGINEERING

2007 - 2012

1999 - 2006

Languages

English: Cambridge First Certificate In English, Level B2 **Spanish:** State Certificate of Language Proficiency, Level B1